https://www.granbyindustries.com/privacy-policy/

Introduction
Welcome to the Website of Granby Industries. Your use of our Website indicates your agreement with the following Terms of Use. If you do not agree to be bound by and comply with these Terms of Use, please do not access or use this Website.
Intellectual Property Notice
This Granby Industries Website, including any content appearing on or accessible through the site, is protected by copyright. Any adaptation, reproduction or distribution thereof is hereby strictly prohibited unless expressly authorized.
Exclusion of Liability
Granby Industries does not warrant the accuracy, relevance or reliability of this Website’s contents, nor does it guarantee that the contents will be available without errors or omissions. The information contained in this Website shall in no circumstances be construed as a legal opinion and Granby Industries is not responsible for any usage thereof.
Privacy Statement
Granby Industries is committed to upholding your right to privacy in accordance with the laws of Québec and Canada respecting the protection of personal information.
Granby Industries may collect personal information about you. Personal data collection is for the exclusive use of the Firm, to allow us to communicate with you, provide you with the services and information you request or provide you with information that may be of interest to you. Unless otherwise authorized by you, Granby Industries will use personal information for these purposes only. If you do not wish to receive additional information, you may advise us accordingly.
Granby Industries
About Us
News & Events
Careers
Partners
Contact Us
Petroleum Tanks
Petroleum tanks – Our Products
Lake or Tank?
